# MUKHAMMADALI TURGUNALIEV

## **CONTACT**

E-MAIL: turgunaliyev.98@gmail.com **GITHUB:** github.com/Muxammadali98

**PHONE:** +998907823396

LINKEDIN: https://www.linkedin.com/in/muxammadali-turgunaliyev/

TELEGRAM: https://t.me/ali98\_uz

## SUMMARY

I have more than 1 year experience as a PHP developer. Furthermore, I have an experience as a Laravel developer. While I work for the company, I learned how to work with a team through the Agile system and Git. Besides that, My math knowledge assists to be more algorithmic.

### **EDUCATION**

College Economic Sep 2014 - Jul 2017

### Professional experiences

**DIGITAL CITY #1** Andijan, Uzbekistan Backend Developer March 2022 -Present

- Attended in several project which are creative, responsive and functional
- Created digital-city.uz for the Company
- Created soosum.uz

**DIGITAL SOFT #2** Andijan, Uzbekistan November 2022 – Present

Backend Developer

- Created <u>a-umar.uz</u> for factory
- Created <u>yuksakobod.uz</u> for building company
- Created miuzbekistan.com online store for mi community

SKILLS AND INTERESTS

Html5/Css

Bootstrap

Php

OOP

MySql

Laravel

Livewire

Git

RestFull API

Languages: Uzbek, English(B1), Russian (B2)